Guide to the Dell Williams papers, 1922-2008.
Williams, Dell papers, 1922-2008
- Series V. Merchandise
  - Vibrator (Box 2)
Harvard Gay & Lesbian Review, The. v.6 no.3.
Hatcher, Robert. Contraceptive Technology: Sixteenth Revised Edition. New York: Irvington Publishers, Inc., 1994.
Hays, H.R. The Dangerous Sex: The Myth of Feminine Evil, 1964.
Herschberger, Ruth. Adam's Rib. New York: Har/Row Books, 1948.
Hogeland, Ronald W., ed. Woman and womanhood in America. Lexington: D.C. Heath and Company, 1973.
Holden, Linsey A. It's Not Mental. 1979.
Hutchins, Loraine.Erotic Rites: A Cultural Analysis of Contemporary U.S. Sacred Sexuality Traditions and Trends. Thesis (Ph. D.)--Union Institute, 2001.
International Who's Who in Sexology. San Francisco: Specific Press, 1986.
The Intimate Explosion, 2 issues.
Iverson, Lucille. Outrage: peoms 1971-1974. Pittsburg: Know, Inc., 1974.
Journal of Sex Research, The, 9 issues.
Kassorla, Irene. Nice Girls Do: and now you can too! Los Angeles: Stratford Press, 1980.
Kay, Ernest, ed. Foremost women of the twentieth century. Cambridge, England: International Biographical Centre, 1988. (includes listing of D.W., p535)
Kerr, Carmen. Sex for Women who want to have fun and loving relationships with equals. New York: Grove Press, Inc., 1977.
Khayyam, Omar (Edward Fitsgerald, tr.). The Rubayyat. Kansas City, MO: Hallmark, 1967.
Kinky Computers: Finding D&S on On-Line Services. Diversified Services, 1994.
Kollontai, Alexandra. Sexual Relations and the Class Struggle; Love and the New Morality. Montpelier, Bristol 6 UK: Falling Wall Press,1972.
Kokopeli, Bruce. Leadership for Change toward a feminist model. Philadelphia: New Society Publishers.
Kronhausen, Phyllis and Eberhard. Erotic Art. New York: Bell Publishing Company, 1967.
Ladas, Alice Kahn et al. The G Spot and other discoveries about human sexuality. New York: Dell Publishing, 1981.
Ladas, Alice Kahn and Harold S. Ladas. Women and Bioenergetic Analysis. Newington, CT: Connecticut Society for Bioenergetic Analysis, 1981.
Lesbian Connection. V.19 no.4-5, v.20 no.2.
Levine, Ellen. All She Needs.... 1973.
"Liberation, Now!: Theme of Women's Liberation." Score. Words by Betty Friedan and Jackqulyn Reinach. Music by Reinach and J. Rene.
Libido: The Journal of Sex and Sensibility, 16 issues, 1988-1995.
Libido. v.1 no.3, v.2 no.1, v.4 no.1, v.6 nos.1-2, v8. no1., v.9 no.4.
Lightfoot-Klein, Hanny. Prisoners of Ritual: An Odyssey into Female Genital Circumcision in Africa. New York: Harrington Park Press,1989.
Loulan, JoAnn. The Lesbian Erotic Dance: Butch, Femme, Androgyny, and Other Rhythms. San Francisco: Spinsters Book Company, 1990.
Lowen, Alexander. The Betrayal of the Body. New York: Collier Books, 1967.
Lusk, Susan. Sappho: The art of loving women. New York: Chelsea House Publishers, 1975.
Maele, Martin Van. The satyrical drawings of Martin Van Maele. New York: The Cythera Press, 1970.
Malinowski, Bronislaw. Sex and Repression in Savage Society. New York: Meridian Books, 1927.
Marcus, Eric:Making History: The Struggle for Gay and Lesbian Equal Rights, 1945-1990. HarperCollins Publishers, 1992.
Meeting In Mexico: World Conference of the International Women's Year. New York: United Nations, 1975.
Miller, Merle. On Being Different: What it Means to Be a Homosexual. New York: Random House, 1971.
Morin, Jack. The Erotic Mind. New York: HarperPerennial, 1995.
Mother Jones. October 1995. New York, NY.
Ms. v.11, no.4.
My First Vibrator: True Life Vibrator Tales. San Francisco: Good Vibrations, 1992.
Natural Way to Health, Vigor, and Beauty, The. New York: Shelton Electric Co., 1917.
Nazarieff, Serge.Der Akt in Der Photographie/The Steroscopic Nude/Le Nu Stéréoscopique: 1890-1930. Spain: Benedikt Taschen Verlag, 1993.
Nefzawi (Shaykh) (Sir Richard F. Burton, tr.). The Perfumed Garden of the Shaykh Nefzawi. New York: Castle Books, 1964.
Nestle, Joan. The persistent desire: a femme-butch reader. Boston: Alyson Publications, Inc., 1992.
Nestle, Joan. A restricted country. Ithaca: Firebrand Books, 1987.
New Directions for Women 1972-1981 [10 year cumulative index], 1982.
New York Law School Law Review, 1993.
Nin, Anaïs. Delta of Venus: Erotica. New York: Harcourt Brace Jovanovich, 1969.
Nomadic Sisters. Loving Women. Mountain View, CA: The Nomadic Sisters, 1976.
NOW Souvenir Journal: 6th Annual Conference. Washington, DC, Feb. 1973.
Offit, Avodah. The Sexual Self. Philadelphia: JB Lippincott Company, 1977.
Olivier, Sigurd and Jeanette Gorrie. Touch love. Sydney, Australia: The amazing aquarian dream factory, 1982.
On Our Backs. 1994: Mar./Apr., Sept./Oct.
Otto, Herbert A. New Orgasm Options Excerpts (Expanding Sexual Pleasure). 1988. (limited edition No. 164, signed by author.)
Paramour: Literary and Artistic Erotica. Vol. 2, No. 4. Parsippany, NJ.
Patton, Cindy. Making It: A Woman's Guide to Sex in the Age of AIDS. Ithaca, NY: Firebrand Books, 1987.
Pearsall, Paul. A Healing Intimacy: The Power of Loving Connections. New York: Crown Trade Paperbacks, 1994.
Penthouse Forum: The International Journal of Human Relations. New York. (5)
Pettigrew, Florida Naomi. Scattered joys. New York: Vantage Press, 1981. (autographed to Dell by author)
Pittenger, Norman. Time for Consent: A Christian's Approach to Homosexuality.
Ploss, Herman Heinrich. Femina Libido Sexualis. New York: The Medical Press, 1965.
Pushkin, A.S. (attributed) Secret Journal, 1836-1837. Minneapolis: M.I.P. Company, 1986.
Redmon, George L. Sensual for Life: The Natural Way to Maintain Sexual Vitality. Neew York: Kensington Publishing Corp., 2003.
Reich, Ilse Ollendorff. Wilhelm Reich: A Personal Biography by Ilse Ollendorff Reich. New York: St. Martin's Press, 1969.
Reich, Wilhelm. The Invasion of Compulsory Sex-Morality. New York: Farrar, Straus and Giroux, 1971.
Reich, Willhelm (Vincent Carfagno, tr.). The Mass Psychology of Fascism. New York: Farrar, Straus & Giroux, 1970.
Reitz, Rosetta. Menopause: A Positive Approach. Radnor, PA: Chilton Book Company, 1977. (page proofs; autographed to Dell by the author)
Ripe: Gay, Lesbian, & Transgender Midlife & Older. May/June 2000 Forest Hills, NY.
Russell, Bertrand. Marriage and Morals. New York: Bantam Books, 1929.
Sathe, R.S. Kama-Tantra Prem-Tantra. Pune, Maharashtra, India: Maritosexual and Reproductive Research Institute, 1996.
Schaefer, Leah Cahan. Women and sex. New York: Pantheon Books, 1973.
Schor, Lynda. True Love and Real Romance. New York: Coward, McCann & Geoghegan, 1979.
Sex Panic, The: Women Censorship and "Pornography"; A conference report. New York: National Coalition Against Censorship, 1993.
Simone, Carol. The Goddess of 5th Avenue. San Francisco: Hayden, 2001. (autographed by author)
Slinger, Penny. An Exorcism. London: Villiers Publications Ltd., 1977.
Sochen, June. The New Woman: feminism in Greenwich Village, 1910-1920. New York: Quadrangle Books, 1972.
Steinberg, David, ed. The erotic impulse: honoring the sensual self. Los Angeles: Jeremy P. Tarcher/Perigee, 1992. (page proof)
Sundahl, Deborah.Tantric Journey to Female Orgasm, 1998. VHS
Tantra. Issue #8, 1994.
Tennov, Dorothy. Love and Limerence: The Experience of Being in Love. New York: Stein and Day, 1979.
Truth Seeker, The.. 1989: July/Aug. [special issue on "Crimes of Genital Mutilation"]
Valiente, Doreen. Natural magic. New York: St. Martin's Press, 1975.
Villefranche, Anne-Marie. Plaisir D'Amour. New York: Carroll & Graf Publishers Inc., 1982.
Viva: The International Magazine for Women. November 1975. New York.
Warren, Joyce W. Fanny Fern: an independent woman. New Brunswick, NJ: Rutgers University Press, 1992. (inscribed to Dell by Betty Dodson)
Weintraub, Joseph, ed. The Wit and Wisdom of Mae West. New York: G.P. Putnam's Sons, 1967.
Williams, Dell and Lynn Vannucci. Revolution in the Garden: Memoirs of the Gardenkeeper. Hong Kong: Silverback Books, Inc., n.d.
Witch's OS, The. Lolly Hirsch, 1972.
Womanspeak. v.2, v.4.
Women's Sexuality Conference: To explore, define and celebrate our own sexuality. New York: NOW, 1973.
Yellow Silk: Journal of Erotic Arts. Albany, CA. (5)
Zacks, Richard. History laid bare: love, sex, and perversity from the Ancient Etruscans to Warren G. Harding. New York: HarperCollins Publishers, 1994.